<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English">
    <!--Weapons_alien-->
        <!--TAR-4A3-->
            <entityname.scp_tar4a3>Fractal Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_tar4a3>
            <entitydescription.scp_tar4a3>A strange looking weapon with unorthodox furniture and ergonomics, evidently not being all that suited for human hands, a slot behind the grip is used to house some sort of battery cell.</entitydescription.scp_tar4a3>
        <!--TBR-6A4-->
            <entityname.scp_tbr6a4>Fractal Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_tbr6a4>
            <entitydescription.scp_tbr6a4>An incredibly weird looking weapon that vaguely resembles some sort of rifle, a slot below the handguard used to house some form of battery cell.</entitydescription.scp_tbr6a4>
        <!--TB-1 pistol-->
            <entityname.scp_tb1>Fractal Hand Cannon</entityname.scp_tb1>
            <entitydescription.scp_tb1>A large and unwieldy Pistol that presumably served as a sidearm for the long gone Fractals, a slot behind where the slide is is used to house some sort of battery cell.</entitydescription.scp_tb1>
        <!--TBSR-7-->
            <entityname.scp_tbsr7>Fractal Anti Materiel Rifle</entityname.scp_tbsr7>
            <entitydescription.scp_tbsr7>A weirdly designed Rifle that is almost impossible to hold correctly due to it's size and weight, a slot behind the grip is used to house some sort of battery cell.</entitydescription.scp_tbsr7>
        <!--TMG12-->
            <entityname.scp_tmg12>Fractal Machine Gun</entityname.scp_tmg12>
            <entitydescription.scp_tmg12>A massive and very unwieldy weapon with a remarkably strange looking feeding system, which also appears to be the housing point of some form of battery cell.</entitydescription.scp_tmg12>
        <!--###-->
            <entityname.scp_fractalbatterycell>Fractal Battery Cell</entityname.scp_fractalbatterycell>
            <entitydescription.scp_fractalbatterycell>A large, very energy dense Battery Cell used to power energy demanding weaponry, using a poorly understood capacitor matrix to contain several megawatts of power inside. Due to their complexity it is impossible to disassemble without destroying the components.</entitydescription.scp_fractalbatterycell>
    <!--Weapons_explosives-->
        <!--A fucking pipebomb-->
            <entityname.scp_pipebomb>Pipe Bomb</entityname.scp_pipebomb>
            <entitydescription.scp_pipebomb>An improvised explosive device that is easy to produce and is popular among Separatist insiders, despite it's low explosive potential compared to standard issue grenades.</entitydescription.scp_pipebomb>
        <!--Defensive Grenade-->
            <entityname.scp_f1>Defensive Fragmentation Grenade</entityname.scp_f1>
            <entitydescription.scp_f1>A large grenade with a thick fragmentation sleeve and large explosive payload, making it hard to throw. It has a 6.5m explosion radius and a 20m frag radius.</entitydescription.scp_f1>
        <!--Durasteel Grenade(?)-->
            <entityname.scp_dm51>Durasteel Fragmentation Grenade</entityname.scp_dm51>
            <entitydescription.scp_dm51>A fragmentation grenade with a Durasteel exterior, creating high velocity AP fragmentation and as a result is ideal against armoured opponents. It has a 4m explosion radius and a 15m frag radius. </entitydescription.scp_dm51>
        <!--Depleted Uranium Grenade-->
            <entityname.scp_m67>DU Fragmentation Grenade</entityname.scp_m67>
            <entitydescription.scp_m67>A baseball style fragmentation grenade with a Depleted Uranium shell, the resulting fragmentation being very effective against body armour. It has a 4.5m explosion radius and a 10m frag radius.</entitydescription.scp_m67>
        <!--M79 Sawed-Off-->
            <entityname.sgt_m79>Sawed-Off Grenade Launcher</entityname.sgt_m79>
            <entitydescription.sgt_m79>A short-and-simple 40mm grenade launcher, used by boarding crews to displace crowds and devastate rooms before lead starts flying. Made for use by one hand.</entitydescription.sgt_m79>
        <!--AG36-->
            <entityname.scp_ag36>Compact Grenade Launcher</entityname.scp_ag36>
            <entitydescription.scp_ag36>A small 40x46mm grenade launcher designed to be a more portable means of explosive ordnance that has greater range than throwing grenades, along with being less bulky than the grenade launcher superceding it. Its compact nature sacrifices velocity and accuracy however.</entitydescription.scp_ag36>
        <!--Rotary Grenade Launcher-->
            <entityname.scp_mgl>Rotary Grenade Launcher</entityname.scp_mgl>
            <entitydescription.scp_mgl>A 40mm Grenade Launcher utilising a 6 round revolving cylinder, whilst providing a massive amount of indirect firepower, the cylinder is liable to fail to cycle.</entitydescription.scp_mgl>
        <!--RPG-7-->
            <entityname.scp_rpg7>Anti-Sub Grenade Launcher</entityname.scp_rpg7>
            <entitydescription.scp_rpg7>A simple 40mm recoilless weapon system based on a Russian design for use against outposts and submarines.</entitydescription.scp_rpg7>
        <!--AT4-->
            <entityname.scp_at4>Disposable Anti-Sub Grenade Launcher</entityname.scp_at4>
            <entitydescription.scp_at4>A lightweight 84mm Disposable Launcher which has become an excellent tool against submarines and outposts, it is loaded with a single HEDP projectile for effect against both groups and armour.</entitydescription.scp_at4>
    <!--Weapons_heavy-->
        <!--Stoner 63 LMG-->
            <entityname.sgt_s63>Combat Light Machine Gun</entityname.sgt_s63>
            <entitydescription.sgt_s63>Another work-around to use Coalition ammunition stores, this 5.56x45 LMG can take both Coalition standard rifle magazines and belt boxes. It's assembly is crude at best, so don't expect much from it.</entitydescription.sgt_s63>
        <!--M249-->
            <entityname.scp_m249>Squad Machine Gun</entityname.scp_m249>
            <entitydescription.scp_m249>An old and boxy 5.56x45mm Light Machine Gun using the same ammunition as the commonly found Tactical Assault Rifle, making ammunition interchangable and accumulated heat lower.</entitydescription.scp_m249>
        <!--PKP Pecheneg-->
            <entityname.scp_pkp>Medium Machine Gun</entityname.scp_pkp>
            <entitydescription.scp_pkp>A somewhat old, heavy but rugged 7.62x51mm GPMG designed for providing powerful sustained fire against a large group of targets.</entitydescription.scp_pkp>
        <!--FN MAG-->
            <entityname.scp_mag>General Purpose Machine Gun</entityname.scp_mag>
            <entitydescription.scp_mag>A heavy and long 7.62x51mm machine gun designed to be a more powerful alternative to the Light Machine Gun, using a rifle cartridge to provide significantly better performance at the cost of more weight and recoil.</entitydescription.scp_mag>
        <!--PKM-->
            <entityname.scp_pkm>Pulemyot</entityname.scp_pkm>
            <entitydescription.scp_pkm>A very old looking 7.62x51mm GPMG, with a custom lightweight bolt carrier and expanded gas tube allowing for a significantly higher fire rate.</entitydescription.scp_pkm>
        <!--RPT-93-->
            <entityname.scp_rpt93>Prototype Heavy Machine Gun</entityname.scp_rpt93>
            <entitydescription.scp_rpt93>A large and powerful 8.6x70mm Heavy Machine Gun, acting as the prime choice for large hordes of creatures or keeping someone pinned down.</entitydescription.scp_rpt93>
        <!--Microgun-->
            <entityname.scp_microgun>Microgun</entityname.scp_microgun>
            <entitydescription.scp_microgun>An incredibly heavy 5.56x45mm Rotary Machine Gun with an internal motor and self-charging battery system.</entitydescription.scp_microgun>
        <!--OSV-96-->
            <entityname.scp_osv96>Crude Anti-Materiel Rifle</entityname.scp_osv96>
            <entitydescription.scp_osv96>A 12.7x99mm Anti-Materiel Rifle made to be more of an accessible weapon than the Coalition's precision machined, higher quality AMR. Due to the fact that it uses basic parts it is significantly more unwieldy and innacurate, alongside having a horrendous tendency to fail to eject. Regardless it will still fire a 12.7x99mm projectile into an object with considerable lethality.</entitydescription.scp_osv96>
        <!--AR-50-->
            <entityname.scp_ar50>Precision Anti-Materiel Rifle</entityname.scp_ar50>
            <entitydescription.scp_ar50>A very heavy 12.7x99mm, single shot bolt action Anti-Materiel Rifle, capable of taking on significantly larger creatures and penetrating almost any wearable armour.</entitydescription.scp_ar50>
        <!--M107-->
            <entityname.scp_m107>Prototype Anti-Materiel Rifle</entityname.scp_m107>
            <entitydescription.scp_m107>A very large and intimidating 12.7x99mm semi-automatic Anti-Materiel Rifle, the sheer heft of the bolt recoiling back can easily knock someone unprepared off their feet, or worse.</entitydescription.scp_m107>
    <!--Weapons_melee-->
        <!--Bayonet-->
            <entityname.scp_m9bayonet>Combat Knife</entityname.scp_m9bayonet>
            <entitydescription.scp_m9bayonet>A rugged fighting knife intended for hand to hand combat, being significantly more capable than the more common Diving Knife.</entitydescription.scp_m9bayonet>
        <!--Machete-->
            <entityname.scp_machete>Machete</entityname.scp_machete>
            <entitydescription.scp_machete>A multi-purpose blade originally designed for combat and cutting through fauna. Unlike most blades this has the capability of penetrating armour to some degree.</entitydescription.scp_machete>
        <!--Dementonite Machete-->
            <entityname.scp_dementonitemachete>Dementonite Machete</entityname.scp_dementonitemachete>
            <entitydescription.scp_dementonitemachete>A heavy and sturdy blade capable of inflicting significantly more damage upon unarmoured and armoured targets alike.</entitydescription.scp_dementonitemachete>
        <!--Physicorium Tactical Sword-->
            <entityname.scp_physicoriumsword>Physicorium Tactical Sword</entityname.scp_physicoriumsword>
            <entitydescription.scp_physicoriumsword>A large yet light blade made of Physicorium, capable of cutting through significant amounts of armour.</entitydescription.scp_physicoriumsword>
        <!--Batong-->
            <entityname.scp_baton>Baton</entityname.scp_baton>
            <entitydescription.scp_baton>A simple collapsable steel baton with a rubber coating, for use as a cheap, non-lethal means of discouragement.</entitydescription.scp_baton>
        <!--Submission Batong-->
            <entityname.scp_submissionbaton>Submission Baton</entityname.scp_submissionbaton>
            <entitydescription.scp_submissionbaton>A heavy duty baton capable of storing a significantly more power for quickly disabling a dangerous individual. Its large capacitors require metal shielding around the base of the baton for durability's sake, increasing weight and making it more difficult to wield.</entitydescription.scp_submissionbaton>
        <!--Sledgehammer-->
            <entityname.scp_sledge>Sledgehammer</entityname.scp_sledge>
            <entitydescription.scp_sledge>A large, heavy tool used for bashing down doors or breaking hulls though can be used as an improvised weapon.</entitydescription.scp_sledge>
        <!--Crank that soulja boy-->
            <entityname.sgt_wrench>Utility Wrench</entityname.sgt_wrench>
            <entitydescription.sgt_wrench>A stronger and more balanced durasteel wrench.</entitydescription.sgt_wrench>
        <!--Greytide Stationwide-->
            <entityname.sgt_toolbox>Toolkit</entityname.sgt_toolbox>
            <entitydescription.sgt_toolbox>A toolbox containing everything needed for repairs and fieldwork, with a few open pockets for stowing additional supplies. It's made of Iron. It's very Robust.</entitydescription.sgt_toolbox>
        <!--(Dura)Steel Crowbar-->
            <entityname.sgt_crowbar>Durasteel Crowbar</entityname.sgt_crowbar>
            <entitydescription.sgt_crowbar>A weighty and durable wrecking bar made from durasteel. Sometimes it has to be a crowbar coming at them down a steel corridor.</entitydescription.sgt_crowbar>
    <!--Weapons_pistols-->
        <!--SIG P226-->
            <entityname.scp_p226>Service Pistol</entityname.scp_p226>
            <entitydescription.scp_p226>A 9x19mm recoil-operated pistol. It is a near fool-proof design found all across Europa, being adopted by the Coalition as its primary sidearm despite the cartridge's inherently lackluster capabilities.</entitydescription.scp_p226>
        <!--MP443-->
            <entityname.scp_mp443>Civilian Pistol</entityname.scp_mp443>
            <entitydescription.scp_mp443>A boxy 9x19mm pistol seen in the hands of separatists given it's less complex nature and ease of disassembly, though such rudimentary parts are prone to heat retention.</entitydescription.scp_mp443>
        <!--Glock 17-->
            <entityname.scp_g17>Gaston</entityname.scp_g17>
            <entitydescription.scp_g17>A rather blocky but reliable 9x19mm pistol, evidently being an older design of self-loading pistol. It has kept surprisingly intact despite it's apparent age.</entitydescription.scp_g17>
        <!--Ruger-9-->
            <entityname.scp_ruger9>Prototype Pistol</entityname.scp_ruger9>
            <entitydescription.scp_ruger9>A sleek and compact 9x19mm pistol that is essentially a glorified machine pistol, providing excellent firepower and superior accuracy compared to other autoloading handguns. However it's calibre is it's primary downside, having poor effect against armour.</entitydescription.scp_ruger9>
        <!--Hi-Point Pistol-->
            <entityname.sgt_hpp>Civilian Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_hpp>
            <entitydescription.sgt_hpp>Designed to fire 10x25mm, the "Plastic Pistol" has lead weights in its' slide to cycle properly, giving it a weighty feel, though doing nothing for the recoil.</entitydescription.sgt_hpp>
        <!--USP 10mm-->
            <entityname.sgt_usp>Combat Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_usp>
            <entitydescription.sgt_usp>A boxy looking 10x25mm handgun, being favoured by most Coalition operators for it's substantially better power and penetration than both 9x19 and 11.43x23 pistols. Such power however comes at the cost of a heavy pistol and significant recoil impulses that most shooters can't handle.</entitydescription.sgt_usp>
        <!--Mk23 SOCOM 10mm-->
            <entityname.sgt_mk23>Covert Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_mk23>
            <entitydescription.sgt_mk23>A 10x25mm combat pistol, with integrated light and suppressor for use by Coalition Black-Ops. Needing something maneuverable, but hardy to keep as backup, the employment of more expensive alloys helps to lighten the overall weapon without compromising reliability.</entitydescription.sgt_mk23>
        <!--N99 Pistol-->
            <entityname.sgt_n99>The Wanderer</entityname.sgt_n99>
            <entitydescription.sgt_n99>This 10x25mm pistol has seen some better days, with dents and scratches from every discernable source, but just as reliable as ever. Recoil is extremely manageable, so don't worry about a Kick in the Head.</entitydescription.sgt_n99>
        <!--Auto 10-->
            <entityname.sgt_auto10>Prototype Assault Pistol</entityname.sgt_auto10>
            <entitydescription.sgt_auto10>An unorthodox 10x25mm design, with ported barrel and weight distribution for ease of handling during firing. It fires in 2-round bursts to maximize rounds on target, with it doing nothing more but a gentle bounce during its' function.</entitydescription.sgt_auto10>
        <!--Colt Python-->
            <entityname.scp_python>Service Revolver</entityname.scp_python>
            <entitydescription.scp_python>A 9x33mm revolver utilising a larger, higher pressure cartridge than the Coalition's older defensive revolver, but can also use its predecessor's cartridges. It has a light double action trigger mechanism.</entitydescription.scp_python>
        <!--R8-->
            <entityname.scp_r8>Aftermarket Service Revolver</entityname.scp_r8>
            <entitydescription.scp_r8>A modified 9x33mm Service Revolver that has been almost entirely overhauled, featuring a light trigger and an 8 round cylinder.</entitydescription.scp_r8>
        <!--Ruger Super Blackhawk-->
            <entityname.sgt_gunslinger>Single-Action Light Hand Cannon</entityname.sgt_gunslinger>
            <entitydescription.sgt_gunslinger>A 10.9x33mmR Single-Action revolver, great choice for self-defense, due to it's light trigger pull, but requires the hammer to be drawn back for every subsequent shot. However, the simplicity allows for single-handed use, and more skilled individuals can re-balance it in their hands faster, allowing for quicker shots.</entitydescription.sgt_gunslinger>
        <!--Colt Anaconda-->
            <entityname.scp_anaconda>Light Hand Cannon</entityname.scp_anaconda>
            <entitydescription.scp_anaconda>A 10.9x33mm revolver featuring a long barrel and larger cartridge than the Service Revolver. It has a moderately heavy double action trigger mechanism.</entitydescription.scp_anaconda>
        <!--M29-->
            <entityname.scp_m29>Lucky Punk</entityname.scp_m29>
            <entitydescription.scp_m29>An old 10.9x33mm revolver that looks relatively well kept.</entitydescription.scp_m29>
        <!--SR1-->
            <entityname.scp_sr1>Civilian Heavy Pistol</entityname.scp_sr1>
            <entitydescription.scp_sr1>An 11.43x23mm pistol used as an easily producable version of the Coalition's Heavy Pistol, with evidence to it originally not being produced in this cartridge. Due to less precision machining it is less accurate alongside having a weaker recoil spring, however this has the side effect of allowing the slide to cycle faster.</entitydescription.scp_sr1>
        <!--MEU(SOC)-->
            <entityname.scp_meusoc>Military Heavy Pistol</entityname.scp_meusoc>
            <entitydescription.scp_meusoc>An 11.43x23mm recoil operated pistol derived from an old American design, using a cartridge which provides more energy on target than 9mm pistol cartridges.</entitydescription.scp_meusoc>
        <!--USP 45-->
            <entityname.scp_usp45>Seitenwaffe</entityname.scp_usp45>
            <entitydescription.scp_usp45>A rather blocky 11.4x23mm pistol likely of Separatist origin, being heavily modified by the previous owner.</entitydescription.scp_usp45>
        <!--FNX-45-->
            <entityname.scp_fnx45>Prototype Heavy Pistol</entityname.scp_fnx45>
            <entitydescription.scp_fnx45>A finely tuned 11.43x23mm pistol with a light slide, reinforced Durasteel recoil spring and crisp competition grade trigger, allowing for fast and accurate shots. Despite these inherent advantages over it's predecessor, it's round still performs horrendously against any sort of armour.</entitydescription.scp_fnx45>
        <!--Desert Eagle-->
            <entityname.scp_deagle>Oppressor Heavy Pistol</entityname.scp_deagle>
            <entitydescription.scp_deagle>A large and unweidly 12.7x33mm pistol. It is carried around by individuals to show superiority as a result of its intimidating profile and price tag.</entitydescription.scp_deagle>
        <!--M6 Halo Magnum-->
            <entityname.scp_m6>Prototype Oppressor Heavy Pistol</entityname.scp_m6>
            <entitydescription.scp_m6>A strange but elegant 12.7x33mm design for a powerhouse of a handgun, with state-of-the-art closed bolt mechanism and Durasteel recoil spring able to significantly dampen the recoil impulses.</entitydescription.scp_m6>
        <!--Rsh-12-->
            <entityname.scp_rsh50>Hand Breaker</entityname.scp_rsh50>
            <entitydescription.scp_rsh50>A 12.7x99mm Assault Revolver that has been modified to take Anti-Materiel Cartridges, who did this and why is unknown given the ridiculous recoil.</entitydescription.scp_rsh50>
        <!--Magnus-->
            <entityname.scp_magnus>Prototype Assault Revolver</entityname.scp_magnus>
            <entitydescription.scp_magnus>An Assault Revolver utilizing an unorthodox and unconventional cylinder and barrel to allow for firing 9x33, 10.9x33 and 12.7x55mm cartridges. As a result of the strange trigger linkage to the cylinder it takes a lot of skill to fire quickly.</entitydescription.scp_magnus>
        <!--AR-15 Pistol-->
            <entityname.sgt_arpistol>Prototype Short-Barreled Rifle</entityname.sgt_arpistol>
            <entitydescription.sgt_arpistol>Chambered in the intermediate 5.56x45, it has native armor piercing and capacity over any other pistol, but at the cost of a larger profile.</entitydescription.sgt_arpistol>
        <!--ASh-12.7 Pistol-->
            <entityname.sgt_bolter>Prototype Oppressor Battle Carbine</entityname.sgt_bolter>
            <entitydescription.sgt_bolter>A short rifle that runs on 12.7x55 by means of magazines. It adapts upon the Coalition's favored Oppressor Battle Rifle, built into a smaller package while increasing efficiency of gas usage, allowing it to top-out at a higher rate of fire. This also causes it to jump violently, oftentimes injuring untrained users.</entitydescription.sgt_bolter>
    <!--Weapons_rifles-->
        <!--.38 Levergun-->
            <entityname.sgt_levergun>Service Repeater</entityname.sgt_levergun>
            <entitydescription.sgt_levergun>A 9x29mm rifle utilizing a very old lever action system that is heavily outdated compared to most firearms on Europa. Despite the inherent antiquity, it is favoured by Coalition captains and citizens for making a rather puny cartridge more viable with it's longer barrel and 9 round tube.</entitydescription.sgt_levergun>
        <!--Henry Tactical-->
            <entityname.sgt_henrytac>Prototype Repeater</entityname.sgt_henrytac>
            <entitydescription.sgt_henrytac>A heavily updated, multi-calibre Repeater capable of chambering 9x29, 9x33 and 10.9x33, making it significantly more versatile at the cost of a complicated lever and bolt system that needs some decent skill to cycle correctly.</entitydescription.sgt_henrytac>
        <!--AKS-74U-->
            <entityname.scp_aks74u>Crude Assault Carbine</entityname.scp_aks74u>
            <entitydescription.scp_aks74u>A rugged 5.45x39mm Assault Carbine for use in confined spaces. It is easily concealable alongside having a high fire rate, however is very inaccurate and has a significantly higher gas intake.</entitydescription.scp_aks74u>
        <!--AK-74M-->
            <entityname.scp_ak74m>Crude Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_ak74m>
            <entitydescription.scp_ak74m>A rugged 5.45x39mm Assault Rifle that has become a primary armament for the Separatists. Being easily produced and hidden away, this rifle is the go-to for a quick and basic mugging or mutiny.</entitydescription.scp_ak74m>
        <!--SG550-->
            <entityname.scp_sg550>Combat Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_sg550>
            <entitydescription.scp_sg550>A standard issue 5.56x45mm Assault Rifle designed to be a general purpose weapon for flexibility in almost any situation. It is a very common sight on submarines and in the hands of Coalition forces.</entitydescription.scp_sg550>
        <!--SG550 (military)-->
            <entityname.scp_sg550mli>Aftermarket Coalition Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_sg550mli>
            <entitydescription.scp_sg550mli>A heavily modified Coalition AR with substantially better furniture, being rechambered for 6.5x39mm to further increase it's viability.</entitydescription.scp_sg550mli>
        <!--G36C-->
            <entityname.scp_g36c>Karabiner</entityname.scp_g36c>
            <entitydescription.scp_g36c>A 5.56x45mm Assault Carbine that was once used by the Coalition, however the Separatists used this design for their Precision AR.</entitydescription.scp_g36c>
        <!--Kel-Tec M35A2-->
            <entityname.scp_m35a2>Hammerhead</entityname.scp_m35a2>
            <entitydescription.scp_m35a2>A strangely pristine 5.56x45mm Bullpup Assault Rifle. Hailing from a cancelled Coalition weapons program from recent events, these rifles are incredibly rare despite their overall superior characteristics to the current issue rifles.</entitydescription.scp_m35a2>
        <!--M16A3 Grenadier-->
            <entityname.scp_m16a3>Stormer</entityname.scp_m16a3>
            <entitydescription.scp_m16a3>An old and battle worn 5.56x45mm Assault Rifle that looks heavily used by it's previous owner and features a 40mm Grenade Launcher.</entitydescription.scp_m16a3>
        <!--G36-->
            <entityname.scp_g36>Automatic Precision Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_g36>
            <entitydescription.scp_g36>A 5.56x45mm Assault Rifle that is quite well designed for a Separatist weapon, using the Coalition's cartridge of choice for better accuracy. Whilst it's better in close quarters than it's more precise and burst fire Coalition counterpart, it's polymer furniture is awful for heat regulation.</entitydescription.scp_g36>
        <!--Desert Tech MDR-->
            <entityname.scp_mdr>Burst Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_mdr>
            <entitydescription.scp_mdr>A 5.56x45mm Assault Rifle in a bullpup configuration designed to house a full length barrel within a package the same size as a conventional rifle, it has found favourites despite the burst trigger mechanism meant to conserve ammo.</entitydescription.scp_mdr>
        <!--F2000-->
            <entityname.sgt_f2k>Coalition Suppressed Assault Rifle</entityname.sgt_f2k>
            <entitydescription.sgt_f2k>A highly unusual looking suppressed 5.56x45mm rifle featuring an unconventional ejection system and somewhat alien shape, alongside having a full rifle length barrel in a more compact package. Produced for Black Ops who require a covert weapon that uses more available ammunition.</entitydescription.sgt_f2k>
        <!--HK433-->
            <entityname.scp_hk433>Prototype Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_hk433>
            <entitydescription.scp_hk433>A lightweight 5.56x45mm Assault Rifle with an excellent cyclic rate and accuracy without producing significant recoil due to its calibre and muzzle brake. Comes with a 40mm UGL.</entitydescription.scp_hk433>
        <!--KH2020-->
            <entityname.scp_kh2020>Bullpup Caseless Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_kh2020>
            <entitydescription.scp_kh2020>A 6.5x39mm Bullpup Assault Rifle favoured by the more notable Separatist members given it's balance between power and fire rate. It is however much less accurate than it's conventional counterpart despite the same barrel length in a more compact package.</entitydescription.scp_kh2020>
        <!--CMMG MXA1-->
            <entityname.scp_mxa1>Tactical Caseless Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_mxa1>
            <entitydescription.scp_mxa1>A mostly polymer 6.5x39mm Assault Rifle using an unusual cartridge and acts as a stop-gap between 5.56 and 7.62mm rifles. Whilst not as prolific as its conventional counterparts given it's very poor heat convection, it has found some favourites due to its accuracy and low weight.</entitydescription.scp_mxa1>
        <!--SA80A3-->
            <entityname.scp_sa80a3>Imperialist</entityname.scp_sa80a3>
            <entitydescription.scp_sa80a3>A 6.5x39mm Assault Rifle based on a British design with a bullpup configuration, providing greater accuracy and velocity, though noticably increases recoil.</entitydescription.scp_sa80a3>
        <!--CMMG MXA3-->
            <entityname.scp_mxa3>Prototype Caseless Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_mxa3>
            <entitydescription.scp_mxa3>A heavy revised Caseless Assault Rifle designed to overcome the flaws of the previous design, utilizing lighter and tougher durasteel recoil springs and a 40mm Grenade Launcher for greater offensive capabilities.</entitydescription.scp_mxa3>
        <!--AK-103-->
            <entityname.scp_ak103>Aggressor Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_ak103>
            <entitydescription.scp_ak103>A rugged and highly infamous 7.62x39mm Assault Rifle that has become an icon of the Separatist movement, it's relative ease of manufacturing and powerful cartridges making it the go-to choice for an insurrection against armoured belligerents.</entitydescription.scp_ak103>
        <!--AKMS-->
            <entityname.scp_akms>Avtomat</entityname.scp_akms>
            <entitydescription.scp_akms>A very old looking 7.62x39mm rifle using a very uncomfortable folding stock and primitive muzzle brake. The wood handguard is in surprisingly good shape given where it came from.</entitydescription.scp_akms>
        <!--AK-103 Custom-->
            <entityname.scp_akliv>Vanguard Oppressor Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_akliv>
            <entitydescription.scp_akliv>A heavily modified Renegade Oppressor AR chambered in 7.62x39mm, with a custom gas block and more ergonomic furniture.</entitydescription.scp_akliv>
        <!--AK-15 Custom-->
            <entityname.scp_ak15zlobin>Prototype Aggressor Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_ak15zlobin>
            <entitydescription.scp_ak15zlobin>A modernized Aggressor Assault Rifle, featuring heavily updated furniture and an unconventional magwell and auto-regulating gas system, able to feed both 7.62x39mm and 5.45x39mm cartridges. Comes with a 40mm UGL.</entitydescription.scp_ak15zlobin>
        <!--G3-->
            <entityname.scp_g3>Heavy Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_g3>
            <entitydescription.scp_g3>A 7.62x51mm Battle Rifle based off an old German design and is used predominantly by the Separatists, with it's longer barrel providing more muzzle energy. However, the weapon uses a large, heavy bolt and off-axis stock, which significantly worsens recoil.</entitydescription.scp_g3>
        <!--SCAR-H / SCAR-17-->
            <entityname.scp_scar17>Combat Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_scar17>
            <entitydescription.scp_scar17>A large 7.62x51mm short stroke Battle Rifle chambering a powerful, battle tested cartridge. It is favoured by Coalition members who use it given it's effectiveness against both unarmoured and armoured targets.</entitydescription.scp_scar17>
        <!--G3KA4-->
            <entityname.scp_g3ka4>Sturmgewehr</entityname.scp_g3ka4>
            <entitydescription.scp_g3ka4>A compact 7.62x51mm Battle Rifle utilising a roller delayed blowback operation for more reliable cycling, however requires an overall heavier bolt to accomplish, increasing recoil impulses.</entitydescription.scp_g3ka4>
        <!--7.62x51 VHS-->
            <entityname.sgt_vhs>Coalition Suppressed Battle Rifle</entityname.sgt_vhs>
            <entitydescription.sgt_vhs>Loading 7.62x51, Coalition Black-Ops teams needed something with more "Knockdown Potential," in a more compact package. The bullpup design was used to keep the weapon relatively small and light, alongside integral suppressors to mask their presence when deep in enemy territory. The weapon uses a quick 4-round burst firemode to help with overall accuracy, and reduce ammunition waste.</entitydescription.sgt_vhs>
        <!--MA-37-->
            <entityname.scp_ma37>Prototype Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_ma37>
            <entitydescription.scp_ma37>A 7.62x51mm Battle Rifle in a bullpup configuration, housing a full sized barrel for maximum cartridge effectiveness.</entitydescription.scp_ma37>
        <!--Tabuk-->
            <entityname.scp_tabuk>Crude Marksman Rifle</entityname.scp_tabuk>
            <entitydescription.scp_tabuk>A 7.62x39mm Marksman Rifle based off of the Separatist's mainstay Assault Rifle. It is a strange choice given the calibre it uses has poor long range ballistic coefficiency, however that evidently doesn't stop the Separatists.</entitydescription.scp_tabuk>
        <!--SCAR20-->
            <entityname.scp_scar20>Combat Marksman Rifle</entityname.scp_scar20>
            <entitydescription.scp_scar20>A 7.62x51mm Marksman Rifle based off of the Battle Rifle, providing a longer free floating barrel for excellent accuracy, the large optic and long dimensions however make it very difficult for an inexperienced user to quickly fire accurately.</entitydescription.scp_scar20>
        <!--DMR-540-->
            <entityname.scp_dmr540>Raptor</entityname.scp_dmr540>
            <entitydescription.scp_dmr540>A highly modernized 7.62x51mm Marksman Rifle hailing from the same failed weapons program as the Hammerhead, being made to replace both the Battle Rifle and the Marksman Rifle. As this rifle is no longer produced, it is extremely rare.</entitydescription.scp_dmr540>
        <!--M1 Garand-->
            <entityname.sgt_rifle>Semi-Auto Rifle</entityname.sgt_rifle>
            <entitydescription.sgt_rifle>A stark comparison to the more reliable bolt-action Coalition counterpart, it has a deeper internal magazine, with a self-actuating bolt. The gas system is incredibly rudimentary, and pulls enough away from the round to cause decreased performance.</entitydescription.sgt_rifle>
        <!--M24/Remington 700 Magnum-->
            <entityname.scp_m24>Revised Precision Rifle</entityname.scp_m24>
            <entitydescription.scp_m24>An 8.6x70mm rifle made to be an alternative to the Coalition's more fine-crafted Precision Rifle. The cartridge's recoil is intense as it clearly was a design that wasn't meant to use it.</entitydescription.scp_m24>
        <!--Orsis T-5000-->
            <entityname.scp_t5000>Military Precision Rifle</entityname.scp_t5000>
            <entitydescription.scp_t5000>A large 8.6x70mm rifle designed for quickly and precisely taking out a single person, it is a rare sight on Europa given it's long range nich is very situational.</entitydescription.scp_t5000>
        <!--PMR-->
        <!--SVCh-->
            <entityname.sgt_ppr>Prototype Precision Rifle</entityname.sgt_ppr>
            <entitydescription.sgt_ppr>A semi-automatic 8.6x70mm rifle that neatly fits the Designated Marksman role, it has the ability to force through the majority of helmets and vests, while being quick enough for follow-up shots, in the case that one isn't enough.</entitydescription.sgt_ppr>
        <!--AS Val-->
            <entityname.scp_val>Covert Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_val>
            <entitydescription.scp_val>A 9x39mm Assault Rifle with an integral suppressor designed for close quarters, being favoured by both the Separatists and Coalition for it's close range lethality. The suppressor however retains a massive amount of heat despite the subsonic ammunition.</entitydescription.scp_val>
        <!--XMS-->
            <entityname.sgt_xms>Coalition Covert Combat Rifle</entityname.sgt_xms>
            <entitydescription.sgt_xms>An odd rifle loading the natively subsonic 9x39, it squeezes every bit of extra energy for the round, giving it more power and armor piercing. It's cyclical rate is somewhat low, designed to keep it little more than a hoarse whisper, to the preference of Black-Ops Operatives.</entitydescription.sgt_xms>
        <!--SR-3 Vihkr-->
            <entityname.scp_sr3>Infiltrator Covert Assault Rifle</entityname.scp_sr3>
            <entitydescription.scp_sr3>A custom built 9x39mm assault rifle using a Covert AR as a base, featuring a Physicorium baffle suppressor for excellent heat properties whilst retaining a good rate of fire.</entitydescription.scp_sr3>
        <!--Malyuk-12-->
            <entityname.scp_malyuk12>Aggressor Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_malyuk12>
            <entitydescription.scp_malyuk12>A semi-crude looking 12.7x55mm AK style rifle, evidently being a more available option for the Separatists. It fires significantly faster though as a result puts a lot of demand on the shooter.</entitydescription.scp_malyuk12>
        <!--ASh-12.7-->
            <entityname.scp_ash12>Oppressor Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_ash12>
            <entitydescription.scp_ash12>A top of the line Bullpup 12.7x55mm Battle Rifle designed for close quarter engagements, making it a favourite for assault teams for attacking vessels and outposts. Due to the cartridge and operating system however, feeding issues can quickly arise.</entitydescription.scp_ash12>
        <!--ASh-12.7 (Custom)-->
            <entityname.scp_ash12unique>Protectorate Oppressor Battle Rifle </entityname.scp_ash12unique>
            <entitydescription.scp_ash12unique>An Oppressor Battle Rifle heavily modified by a Protectorate, having a custom gas tube for a significantly higher fire rate and a custom muzzle brake to mitigate the added recoil somewhat.</entitydescription.scp_ash12unique>
        <!--ASP-1 Kir-->
            <entityname.scp_kir>Infiltrator Oppressor Battle Rifle</entityname.scp_kir>
            <entitydescription.scp_kir>An Oppressor Battle Rifle heavily modified for assassinations, featuring a semi-auto control group and an experimental Physicorium baffle suppressor, which almost entirely neutralizes heat retention.</entitydescription.scp_kir>
    <!--Weapons_shotguns-->
        <!--RM93-->
            <entityname.scp_rm93>Civilian Pump Action Shotgun</entityname.scp_rm93>
            <entitydescription.scp_rm93>A 12 gauge shotgun used by the Separatists when Coalition shotguns aren't an option, featuring a meagre 6 round tube and a semi-stiff pump action. Regardless it gets the job done in a similar fashion.</entitydescription.scp_rm93>
        <!--Mossberg 590-->
            <entityname.scp_m590>Tactical Pump Action Shotgun</entityname.scp_m590>
            <entitydescription.scp_m590>A common 12 gauge shotgun mainly used as a more robust and combat effective alternative to the clunky and dated Riot Shotgun that preceded it.</entitydescription.scp_m590>
        <!--KSG-12-->
            <entityname.scp_ksg>Oppressor Shotgun</entityname.scp_ksg>
            <entitydescription.scp_ksg>A modern 12 gauge pump action shotgun derived from an unconventional American design, utilising 2 switchable tubes allowing for significantly greater capacity over most shotguns.</entitydescription.scp_ksg>
        <!--UTS-15-->
            <entityname.scp_uts15>Prototype Oppressor Shotgun</entityname.scp_uts15>
            <entitydescription.scp_uts15>A heavy and boxy 12 Gauge shotgun with unprecidented capacity and close range firepower compared to other shotguns, making it perfect for dealing with a particularly hardy enemy or a large group of targets.</entitydescription.scp_uts15>
        <!--Domique-->
            <entityname.scp_domique>Domique</entityname.scp_domique>
            <entitydescription.scp_domique>A very old 12 gauge shotgun being one the first examples of dual environment bolt systems, it was a standard issue gun for security until more capable firearms were adapted and produced.</entitydescription.scp_domique>
        <!--Saiga 12-->
            <entityname.scp_saiga12>Mag-Fed Combat Shotgun</entityname.scp_saiga12>
            <entitydescription.scp_saiga12>A 12 Gauge magazine fed combat shotgun, is much easier to load to full with it's dedicated magazines, but has significant recoil due to the basic AK style recoil system.</entitydescription.scp_saiga12>
        <!--M4 Super 90-->
            <entityname.scp_m4s90>Semi-Auto Combat Shotgun</entityname.scp_m4s90>
            <entitydescription.scp_m4s90>A high quality 12 Gauge Semi Automatic Shotgun which has a large magazine tube and can fire relatively quickly.</entitydescription.scp_m4s90>
        <!--Spas-12 (AUTOMATIC)-->
            <entityname.scp_spas12>Franchi</entityname.scp_spas12>
            <entitydescription.scp_spas12>A blocky 12 gauge shotgun with no stock, though is able to quickly empty its tube at anything unfortunate enough to be close.</entitydescription.scp_spas12>
        <!--Origin-12-->
        <!--AA12-->
            <entityname.scp_aa12>Prototype Combat Shotgun</entityname.scp_aa12>
            <entitydescription.scp_aa12>An advanced 12 Gauge Semi-Automatic shotgun feeding from Combat Shotgun magazines, capable of quickly decimating anything inside a corridor or nest. The trigger however is extremely clunky for an individual not used to it.</entitydescription.scp_aa12>
        <!--Double-Barrel 8-Gauge-->
            <entityname.sgt_dbs>Double-Barrel Assault Shotgun</entityname.sgt_dbs>
            <entitydescription.sgt_dbs>A retooled Double-Barrel shotgun, favored by Veterans of any side for it's reliability and commanding feel. With the ability to quickly drop both 8-Gauge shells in a moments notice, it often gets used in a defensive manner, as exchanging shells takes a while-too-long for gunfights.</entitydescription.sgt_dbs>
        <!--SP-12 8-Gauge (Was M90 Tactical)-->
            <entityname.sgt_m90t>Pump-Action Assault Shotgun</entityname.sgt_m90t>
            <entitydescription.sgt_m90t>Designed for multi-role, the Assault Shotgun has a long and complicated service history. Sporting the 8-Gauge shell, it has a nasty habit of breaking faces, doors, and the occasional shoulder, as it's recoil is unforgiving, though there are some who take no less for traitors.</entitydescription.sgt_m90t>
        <!--KS-23-->
            <entityname.scp_ks23>Big Bore Shotgun</entityname.scp_ks23>
            <entitydescription.scp_ks23>A 6 Gauge powerhouse of a Shotgun that uses the largest shotgun shell considered practical. It has a small capacity however fires shells that hit like an entire submarine.</entitydescription.scp_ks23>
    <!--Weapons_smgs-->
        <!--Uzi-->
            <entityname.scp_uzi>Compact Submachine Gun</entityname.scp_uzi>
            <entitydescription.scp_uzi>A 9x19mm open bolt Submachine Gun hailing from a simple stamped steel design, making it significantly easier to produce, however sacrifices ergonomics and accuracy as a result.</entitydescription.scp_uzi>
        <!--SMG-9-->
            <entityname.scp_smg9>Submachine Gun</entityname.scp_smg9>
            <entitydescription.scp_smg9>A compact and easy to operate 9x19mm Submachine Gun designed to provide better accuracy and controllability than a pistol offers. It is a very common weapon in use by civilians and security officers alike.</entitydescription.scp_smg9>
        <!--Vector 9mm-->
            <entityname.scp_vector>Prototype Submachine Gun</entityname.scp_vector>
            <entitydescription.scp_vector>A boxy 9x19mm SMG using a unique delayed blowback operation for recoil mitigation purposes, this allows for an immensely fast hyperburst without the overwhelming recoil.</entitydescription.scp_vector>
        <!--Hi-Point Carbine-->
            <entityname.sgt_hpc>Semi-Auto Assault SMG</entityname.sgt_hpc>
            <entitydescription.sgt_hpc>Firing 10x25mm, it took the design for the Assault Pistol, added a stock, and extended the barrel, allowing for more accurate fire from less skilled individuals.</entitydescription.sgt_hpc>
        <!--APC10-->
            <entityname.sgt_apc>Rapid Assault SMG</entityname.sgt_apc>
            <entitydescription.sgt_apc>Loaded in 10x25mm, the weapon is often favored by boarding parties and ship defense crews for the quick output of damage, while the chunky design and stock mitigate the recoil considerably. The magwell accepts both extended and standard magazine types.</entitydescription.sgt_apc>
        <!--M41A Pulse Rifle-->
            <entityname.sgt_pasmg>Prototype Assault SMG</entityname.sgt_pasmg>
            <entitydescription.sgt_pasmg>A brisk-paced 10x25mm submachine gun with a specialty design, it sacrifices speed for accuracy, leaving the user open to close combat during operations. Though, it seems the 8-Gauge underbarrel was the solution to save this Alien of a weapon.</entitydescription.sgt_pasmg>
        <!--SR2-->
            <entityname.scp_sr2>Compact Heavy Submachine Gun</entityname.scp_sr2>
            <entitydescription.scp_sr2>An 11.43x23mm SMG that has been derived from an already existing SMG design, it is extremely compact however due to the very short barrel accuracy is atrocious.</entitydescription.scp_sr2>
        <!--UMP-45-->
            <entityname.scp_ump45>Heavy Submachine Gun</entityname.scp_ump45>
            <entitydescription.scp_ump45>A boxy 11.43x23mm Submachine Gun suited for close quarters. It uses a larger cartridge and bigger projectile than it's lighter counterpart, but the heavier bolt carrier used reduces firerate in order to accomodate for the higher recoil impulses.</entitydescription.scp_ump45>
        <!--MP9-->
            <entityname.sgt_bosmg>Coalition Suppressed Heavy SMG</entityname.sgt_bosmg>
            <entitydescription.sgt_bosmg>A 11.43x23 SMG with an extreme firerate and integral suppressor, it's favored by Black-Ops Scouts for its quick knock-down and ammo availablity, though it has a nasty habit of running through ammo very quickly, leading to users firing in short, controlled bursts</entitydescription.sgt_bosmg>
    <!--Weapons_special-->
        <!--Chemthrower-->
            <entityname.sgt_chemthrower>Heavy Chemthrower</entityname.sgt_chemthrower>
            <entitydescription.sgt_chemthrower>A large, bulky flamethrower designed by the Coalition to incinerate the most hardy of flora and fauna alike, the specialised chemical fuel reaching up to over 900 degrees and having significantly better range. However it's bulk makes it extremely difficult for a poorly trained user to operate.</entitydescription.sgt_chemthrower>
        <!--Heavy Blaster-->
            <entityname.sgt_heavyblaster>Heavy Blaster</entityname.sgt_heavyblaster>
            <entitydescription.sgt_heavyblaster>An attempt at generalized Man-Portable Laser Weaponry, the clunky "Rifle" needs single-shot disposable cells to fire, due to it's output load required to discharge.</entitydescription.sgt_heavyblaster>
        <!--ASMD Shock Rifle-->
            <entityname.sgt_asmd>Blaster Rifle</entityname.sgt_asmd>
            <entitydescription.sgt_asmd>A more mobile, but unforgiving variant of the Heavy Blaster, allowing a shot to ring instantaniously, but requiring a timely recharge afterwards. Useful for "Fragging" groups of tightly-packed targets.</entitydescription.sgt_asmd>
        <!--Tau Cannon-->
            <entityname.scp_taucannon>Particle Accelerator Cannon</entityname.scp_taucannon>
            <entitydescription.scp_taucannon>A highly experimental device using a miniaturized particle accelerator, fuelled by fissile material cells to lanch high mass elementary particles at .10C, the immense kinetic energy and heat of the projectile capable of blowing most things apart and penetrate deep into materials even with extremely high compressive strength.</entitydescription.scp_taucannon>
        <!--Portable Railgun Cannon-->
            <entityname.scp_railgunlauncher>Portable Railgun Cannon</entityname.scp_railgunlauncher>
            <entitydescription.scp_railgunlauncher>A humongous launcher with large electromagnets that require a huge amount of power, however it can wreak havoc on an unprepared outpost or submarine.</entitydescription.scp_railgunlauncher>
        <!--Portable Coilgun-->
            <entityname.scp_portablecoilgun>Portable Coilgun</entityname.scp_portablecoilgun>
            <entitydescription.scp_portablecoilgun>A very large weapon meant to function as a coilgun, firing a Durasteel slug at high speeds and penetrating several walls and people.</entitydescription.scp_portablecoilgun>
        <!--HCAR-->
            <entityname.sgt_rifleprototype>Prototype Automatic Rifle</entityname.sgt_rifleprototype>
            <entitydescription.sgt_rifleprototype>A more dated design, with some odd touches, it uses a hinged magazine with intent to be fed .30 caliber rounds individually. It's barrel assembly was never truly finished, as it's rifling causes some rounds to yaw in-air, losing penetrative power in the process.</entitydescription.sgt_rifleprototype>
        <!--Nerve Agent-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade1>Nerve Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade1>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade1>Contains a highly lethal gas mixture that can be rapidly absorbed through the skin, making a hazard suit necessary for protection.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade1>
        <!--Syringe Shotgun-->
            <entityname.sgt_syringeshotgun>Syringe Shotgun</entityname.sgt_syringeshotgun>
            <entitydescription.sgt_syringeshotgun>A design questionable by most, it discharges all of it's held syringes in a moments notice. Good for injecting concoxions or intensifying one toxin. Pressure chambers require all others to discharge before they will refill automatically.</entitydescription.sgt_syringeshotgun>
            <entityname.nervegasgrenadeactive>Leaking Nerve Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.nervegasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.nervegasemitter>Nerve Agent Emitter</entityname.nervegasemitter>
        <!--Pulmonary Agent-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade2>Pulmonary Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade2>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade2>Contains a dilute but invariably lethal gas mixture that can be absorbed through the lungs, making respirators sufficient protection. Slow to kill, but near invisible to the naked eye and difficult to treat.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade2>
            <entityname.pulmgasgrenadeactive>Leaking Pulmonary Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.pulmgasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.pulmgasemitter>Pulmonary Agent Emitter</entityname.pulmgasemitter>
        <!--Blood Agent-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade3>Blood Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade3>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade3>Contains a concentrated cyanide-based toxin that causes immediate damage on contact with the skin and absorbs into the blood, making a hazard suit necessary for protection. Rapidly lethal and extremely visible, but long term effects are near non-existent should the victim survive.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade3>
            <entityname.bloodgasgrenadeactive>Leaking Blood Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.bloodgasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.bloodgasemitter>Blood Agent Emitter</entityname.bloodgasemitter>
        <!--Blistering Agent-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade4>Blistering Agent Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade4>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade4>Contains a potent acidic gas mixture that causes immediate burns on contact with the skin, and can build up in the lungs if inhaled, causing severe long term effects. Immediately lethal and very visible, but with long term effects mitigated by a respirator.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade4>
            <entityname.blistergasgrenadeactive>Leaking Blistering Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.blistergasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.blistergasemitter>Blistering Agent Emitter</entityname.blistergasemitter>
        <!--Tear Gas-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade5>Tear Gas Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade5>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade5>Contains a potent irritant capable of causing extreme pain and crippling targets when inhaled. Barely lethal and easy to mitigate with a respirator, but crippling for a moderate period and with instant effect.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade5>
            <entityname.teargasgrenadeactive>Leaking Tear Gas Grenade</entityname.teargasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.teargasemitter>Tear Gas Emitter</entityname.teargasemitter>
        <!--Psychochemical Agent-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade6>Psychochemical Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade6>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade6>Contains a moderately dangerous neurotoxin that causes severe hallucinations and brain damage when inhaled. Low lethality and easy to mitigate with a respirator, but permanently crippling. Some soldiers intentionally inhale small doses for the chemical's psychedelic effects.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade6>
            <entityname.psychogasgrenadeactive>Leaking Psychochemical Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.psychogasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.psychogasemitter>Psychochemical Agent Emitter</entityname.psychogasemitter>
        <!--Incapacitating Agent-->
            <entityname.fenitergasgrenade7>Sedative Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.fenitergasgrenade7>
            <entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade7>Contains potent and rapid-acting sedatives that can cause loss of consciousness seconds after inhalation, but require a moderate dose to have any effect. Completely non-lethal with no long-term effects aswell as being easy to mitigate with a respirator.</entitydescription.fenitergasgrenade7>
            <entityname.sleepgasgrenadeactive>Leaking Sedative Agent Gas Grenade</entityname.sleepgasgrenadeactive>
            <entityname.sleepgasemitter>Sedative Agent Emitter</entityname.sleepgasemitter>
</infotexts>
